# Irene Wu

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER & UX/UI DESIGNER

Email: irenewu222@gmail.com

Portfolio: www.rostrae.ca

Github: www.github.com/irenewuu

#### Skills

Front-end Coding Web Development UX/UI Design Responsive Design User Testing

HTML, CSS
Sass
Styled-Components
Javascript, jQuery
Typescript
Next.js, React.js
Expo
RESTful API
Github, Git
Figma
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Effects

Communication
Collaboration
Organization
Time Management
Problem Solving

Adobe Audition

Adobe Premiere

Adobe InDesign

## Languages

English Mandarin

## Highlights

Front-end developer with two years of experience in closely collaborating with teams in designing and developing interactive and responsive cross platform web applications. Competent in developing web applications incorporating a range of technologies as well as modern libraries and frameworks. Eager to learn new things and use my skills to create quality cross platform web applications.

#### Education

#### Digital Design & Development Diploma

BRITISH COLUMBIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY | SEPTEMBER 2020 - MAY 2022

- Designed and developed interactive, responsive web applications.
- · Collaborated closely with team members for 5+ projects.
- · Wrote clean and organized code while using the best practices.
- Developed strong time management through collaboration with multiple teams in a tight schedule.

## Work Experience

#### Frontend Developer Intern

SCOPEMEDIA | MARCH 2022 - MAY 2022

- Wrote a frontend documentation and laid out various coding standards.
- · Collaborated with the design team to implement new designs.
- · Communicated with lead designer and developer for any frontend problematic issues.
- Worked in an agile environment with daily standup meetings and biweekly sprint planning and sprint retrospectives.

# Project Experience

#### Fullstack Developer, UX/UI Designer

ACNH VILLAGER WISHLIST | JANUARY 2022 - MARCH 2022

- Conducted thorough user testing to create a user-friendly application.
- Connected frontend with backend using RESTful APIs and HTTP requests.
- · Polished the frontend and backend to ensure all functionalities are working.

#### Frontend Developer, UX/UI Designer

KALM | SEPTEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

- Designed and developed a user-friendly, responsive web app.
- Created reusable UI components using React and Styled-components.
- · Worked closely with full-stack developers about the design and front-end.